<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Concepts on VEAF Mission Creation Tools - Documentation</title>
    <link>https://veaf.github.io/VEAF-Mission-Creation-Tools/mission-maker/concepts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Concepts on VEAF Mission Creation Tools - Documentation</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-en</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://veaf.github.io/VEAF-Mission-Creation-Tools/mission-maker/concepts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Load scripts in the mission</title>
      <link>https://veaf.github.io/VEAF-Mission-Creation-Tools/mission-maker/concepts/load-with-triggers/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://veaf.github.io/VEAF-Mission-Creation-Tools/mission-maker/concepts/load-with-triggers/</guid>
      <description>Introduction In a mission using the VEAF Mission Creation Tools, the script have to be loaded through triggers. This chapter will explain how to setup such triggers, and also how to use a dynamic loading method for development.
To load a script in a DCS mission, the easiest way is to create a MISSION START trigger, and make it execute a DO SCRIPT FILE action, loading the script.
If you do this for all the community and veaf scripts, they will be stored in the mission file (in the &amp;ldquo;I10N\default&amp;rdquo; folder) and referenced for loading.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Radio menus</title>
      <link>https://veaf.github.io/VEAF-Mission-Creation-Tools/mission-maker/concepts/radiomenus/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://veaf.github.io/VEAF-Mission-Creation-Tools/mission-maker/concepts/radiomenus/</guid>
      <description>Some of the VEAF Tools scripts add entries to the DCS communication menu (a.k.a the radio menu).
This is the tree-like menu that the player can use to communicate with ATC, the AWACS, the ground crew and other actors in the DCS mission.
The last option in the main menu is always &amp;ldquo;F10. Other&amp;rdquo;. All the custom radio menus will be grouped here.
So, in order for the player to interact with the VEAF scripts using the radio menu, s·he will have to:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>User marks</title>
      <link>https://veaf.github.io/VEAF-Mission-Creation-Tools/mission-maker/concepts/usermarks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://veaf.github.io/VEAF-Mission-Creation-Tools/mission-maker/concepts/usermarks/</guid>
      <description>A lot of the VEAF Mission Creation Tools functionalities are controlled through commands entered in the text of user marks on the F10 map.
This means that, during runtime, a player can go to the F10 map and create a user mark
In this mark, the player enters a text that the VEAF Tools scripts will understand. Of course, it has to follow a specific syntax (see the documentation of the modules) for more detail.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>External scripts</title>
      <link>https://veaf.github.io/VEAF-Mission-Creation-Tools/mission-maker/concepts/externalscripts/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://veaf.github.io/VEAF-Mission-Creation-Tools/mission-maker/concepts/externalscripts/</guid>
      <description>The VEAF Mission Creation Tools contains .lua scripts that are meant to be ran inside a DCS mission, and also other scripts that are meant to run outside a mission.
These scripts are mainly used in the mission building and extraction pipelines (see workflow).
Normalizer DCS mission editor saves the mission data as a set of .lua files compressed in the .miz mission file.
 mission - contains the details of the mission, including all the groups and units.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>