<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Mission maker on VEAF Mission Creation Tools - Documentation</title>
    <link>https://veaf.github.io/VEAF-Mission-Creation-Tools/mission-maker/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Mission maker on VEAF Mission Creation Tools - Documentation</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-en</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://veaf.github.io/VEAF-Mission-Creation-Tools/mission-maker/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>veafAssets</title>
      <link>https://veaf.github.io/VEAF-Mission-Creation-Tools/mission-maker/veafassets/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://veaf.github.io/VEAF-Mission-Creation-Tools/mission-maker/veafassets/</guid>
      <description>Introduction This module creates a radio menu (VEAF / ASSETS) that allows the players to manage the mission air assets.
For each air asset, they can request information (is the asset alive ? What information has the mission maker set up - radio frequencies, TACANs, etc.), respawn the asset (and its eventual linked DCS groups, e.g. escort planes for a High Value Target), dispose of the asset (if set up by the mission maker).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>veafCarrierOperations</title>
      <link>https://veaf.github.io/VEAF-Mission-Creation-Tools/mission-maker/veafcarrieroperations/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://veaf.github.io/VEAF-Mission-Creation-Tools/mission-maker/veafcarrieroperations/</guid>
      <description>Introduction This module creates a radio menu (VEAF / CARRIER OPERATIONS) that allows the players to manage the aircraft carriers (CV) in the mission, at runtime.
For each CV, they can get information (including ATC) and start/end carrier air operations (CAO). During CAO, the CV will sail into the wind at a speed and heading computed to get a specific wind speed right in front of the runway. A rescue helicopter (Pedro) and an emergency tanker can be placed in the mission and will be launched and recovered at appropriate times.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>veafGrass</title>
      <link>https://veaf.github.io/VEAF-Mission-Creation-Tools/mission-maker/veafgrass/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://veaf.github.io/VEAF-Mission-Creation-Tools/mission-maker/veafgrass/</guid>
      <description>Introduction This module helps place a Forward Armament and Refuel Point (FARP) in a mission. It also helps with grass runways (hence its name). The mission creator simply has to place one or few units in the DCS mission editor, and name them following a specific convention; the script will then automatically find and dress these units up at mission start.
How to set up a mission Let&#39;s start by saying that you can clone the VEAF-Demo-Mission repository and use it as an example (or fork it and create a new mission from your fork).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>veafSpawn</title>
      <link>https://veaf.github.io/VEAF-Mission-Creation-Tools/mission-maker/veafspawn/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://veaf.github.io/VEAF-Mission-Creation-Tools/mission-maker/veafspawn/</guid>
      <description>Introduction This module allows the user to spawn several type of DCS objects in a running mission ; it can spawn :
 groups that have been defined with the veafUnits module units that are defined in DCS (either via their veafUnits alias, or their DCS type name dynamic groups that use templates defined with the veafUnits module, but can be configured and are randomized convoys that can go from a point to another, and be tracked and managed with radio commands cargo statics and logistic points that are registered with CTLD and can be transported via helicopter bombs that can destroy scenery, units and groups (even client aircrafts and vehicles) smoke and illumination flares  It also provides commands to :</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>veafUnits</title>
      <link>https://veaf.github.io/VEAF-Mission-Creation-Tools/mission-maker/veafunits/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://veaf.github.io/VEAF-Mission-Creation-Tools/mission-maker/veafunits/</guid>
      <description>Introduction This module allows the user to define groups that can be spawned in a mission using either the veafSpawn, the veafInterpreter or the veafCombatZone modules. It is also possible to define aliases for units that will be used in groups, or spawned directly.
How to set up a mission Let&#39;s start by saying that you can clone the VEAF-Demo-Mission repository and use it as an example (or fork it and create a new mission from your fork).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://veaf.github.io/VEAF-Mission-Creation-Tools/mission-maker/group-list/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://veaf.github.io/VEAF-Mission-Creation-Tools/mission-maker/group-list/</guid>
      <description>Liste des groupes d&#39;unités utilisables dans la mission d&#39;entrainement Groupes définis dans veafUnits    Nom Description Aliases     SA2 SA-2 SAM site &amp;quot;sa2&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;sa-2&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;fs&amp;rdquo;   Rapier Rapier SAM site &amp;quot;rapier_optical&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;rpo&amp;rdquo;   Rapier-radar Rapier SAM site with radar &amp;quot;rapier_radar&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;rpr&amp;rdquo;   SA3 SA-3 SAM site &amp;quot;sa3&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;sa-3&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;lb&amp;rdquo;   SA6 SA-6 SAM site &amp;quot;sa6&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;sa-6&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;06&amp;rdquo;   SA11 SA-11 SAM site &amp;quot;sa11&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;sa-11&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;sd&amp;rdquo;   S300 S300 SAM site &amp;quot;sa10&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;s300&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;bb&amp;rdquo;   Mechanized infantry section Mechanized infantry section with APCs &amp;quot;infantry section&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;infsec&amp;rdquo;   Roland Roland SAM site &amp;quot;roland&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;rd&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;mim-115&amp;rdquo;   Hawk Hawk SAM site &amp;quot;hawk&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;ha&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;mim-23&amp;rdquo;   Patriot Patriot SAM site &amp;quot;patriot&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;pa&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;mim-104&amp;rdquo;    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://veaf.github.io/VEAF-Mission-Creation-Tools/mission-maker/unit-list/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://veaf.github.io/VEAF-Mission-Creation-Tools/mission-maker/unit-list/</guid>
      <description>Liste des unités utilisables dans la mission d&#39;entrainement Unités définies dans DCS Toutes les unités existant dans DCS peuvent être placées par veaf spawn unit ou utilisées dans la définition d&#39;un groupe
Unités définies dans veafUnits    Nom Description Aliases     SA 9 Strela-1 9P31 sa9, sa-9   SA 13 Strela-10M3 sa13, sa-13   SA 6 Kub 2P25 launcher sa6, sa-6   SA 8 Osa 9A33 launcher sa8, sa-8   SA 15 Tor 9A331 sa15, sa-15   Shilka ZSU-23-4 Shilka AAA shilka   Manpad SA-18 Igla-S manpad sa18, sa-18, manpad    </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>